http://www.needpallets.com/privacy

NeedPallets Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy relates to the website www.needpallets.co.uk and governs the privacy of its visitors. It explains how information is collected, stored and how it is used. By using the Services of needpallets.co.uk you confirm you have read and understood the Privacy Policy.APPLICATION OF PRIVACY POLICY I/we totally respect your personal information and will only ask you for information that we really need from you. I/we will look after it in the same way I/we would want ours looking after, keeping it secure. I/we will only share it with others where we need their help to deliver our service to you (such as our professional printing laboratory who may need your name and address to post your purchases). Be assured that we will never share your information in any other circumstances – nor will I/we sell it on elsewhere.NeedPallets takes your privacy very seriously. This privacy policy has been prepared in line with the EU’s General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), which promotes fairness and transparency for all individuals in respect of their personal data. This privacy policy applies to all data we process, and by using our website you consent to our collection and use of such data.WHAT INFORMATION IS BEING COLLECTED? As a data controller, we collect a variety of data in order to deliver our services, and we will manage your personal data transparently, fairly and securely. We may ask you to provide us with the following data – first name, last name, address, postcode, email addresses, IP addresses and contact numbers of the person(s) making an initial enquiry about our services, booking our services or participating in our services.  We collect this data on the following lawful basis to arrange or fulfil a contract and/or to meet a legal obligation other than a contract.  When you visit our website we also collect Cookies. These are small pieces of data that websites send to a user's computer and are stored on the user's web browser. They are designed to enable the website to remember information, such as what a user might have put in a shopping cart for example. This helps us to deliver our service to you. WILL DATA BE SHARED? We share personal data with the following third parties - email provider, accountant,
website manager/hosting company, delivery/postage service providers Data will not be sold to third-party organisations.There are also certain situations in which we may share access to your personal data without your explicit consent; for example, if required by law, to protect the life of an individual, or to comply with any valid legal process, government request, rule or regulation.WHY DO WE SHARE YOUR PERSONAL DATA? We share your data in order to deliver our service to you, to personalise your experience, to provide account access and to for marketing purposes. We may transfer personal data to a country outside of the European Economic Area (EEA) if necessary eg if a third party we utilise could have servers located outside of the EEA. If this is the case, we will either obtain your consent or otherwise ensure that the transfer is legal and your data is secure by following the EU's guidelines. HOW DO WE KEEP YOUR PERSONAL DATA SAFE? We keep your data secure by following internal policies of best practice and by using Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology when information is submitted to us online. In the unlikely event of a criminal breach of our security we will inform the relevant regulatory body within 72 hours and, if your personal data were involved in the breach, we will also inform you. CHANGES TO THE PRIVACY POLICY AND CONTROL We may change this privacy policy from time to time. When we do, we will let you know by changing the date on this policy, notifying customers of only significant changes. By continuing to access or use our services after those changes become effective, you agree to be bound by the revised privacy policy. YOUR RIGHTS AND CHOICES You have the following rights: - - the right to be informed about the collection and use of your personal data- the right of access to your personal data and any supplementary information- the right to have any errors in your personal data rectified- the right to have your personal data erased- the right to block or suppressing the processing of your personal data- the right to move, copy or transfer your personal data from one IT environment to another- the right to object to the processing of your personal data in certain circumstances, and- rights related to automated decision-making (i.e. where no humans are involved) and profiling (i.e. where certain personal data is processed to evaluate an individual).We also give you the option to manage your data via email, telephone and/or writing to us.While we do not hold personal data any longer than we need to, the duration will depend on your relationship with us, and whether it is ongoing. We may keep some of your personal data for up to 7 years after our working contract with you has finished for tax legislation purposes. After this time we may archive your photographs indefinitely along with your relevant details and consent forms. This is due to requests for replacement images being made several years after being taken. ACCESS TO STORED DATAIf you have any questions about the data we hold about you, please feel free to contact us and we will comply with your request as per our legal obligations.FURTHER INFORMATION If you require any further clarification on how we collect, store and process your personal information, please contact us directly. Alternatively, if you would like further information on the legal guidelines we operate within, please refer to the ICO website at https://ico.org.ukOUR DETAILS This business is owned by Trevor Kenny, trading as NeedPallets. You can contact us below
HOME
ABOUT US
OUR SERVICE
WHAT PEOPLE SAY
JOIN US
CONTACT US
Contact us Phone Us - 077321 58670Email Us - trevor@needpallets.com
Privacy Policy
© 2020
All Rights Reserved | NeedPallets
Share by:
